hey everybody Welcome to The Grow Your
Life podcast my name is jeremi Kowski in
this podcast I talk about how coaches
and course creators can scale their
businesses to make more money I want to
talk about nurturing your audience here
today and what that actually means one
of the biggest problems people make is
that they're growing their business
they're growing their email list they're
getting more followers they're building
Their audience but those things don't
matter unless you're building trust and
nurturing a relationship if we look up
the dictionary definition it means to
Foster to develop
a relationship when you're dating you
Foster a relationship the courtship
process and in doing that you get to
connect with another person and go
deeper with them hopefully maybe it
might lead to marriage or just a great
time in the dating
scene same thing happens with friendship
we get to know people trust is
established business is the same
way unless you're selling a widget at
the store which if you're listening to
this podcast probably not what you're
selling you're selling coaching and
courses people need to actually trust
that you're the one that they want to
work with and most people are skeptical
because there's a lot of people that are
out there that are selling courses
training that they shouldn't trust and
they've been burned before and they've
trusted people that really didn't
deliver you know we're thankful that our
clients think that we have one of the
best programs that's out there the
client growth accelerator program that
we have have is one of the best programs
our free classes like the free ads
course that we just released are some of
the best classes that are around people
love our content because we deliver on
what we promise and that's what nurture
is but here's the thing nurture is an
active process it's intentional you have
to be intentional to make and develop
that connection now you can do so with
the content that you produce now not
everybody is going to want to be
nurtured and that's not your job job
really to kind of control that process
your job is to do the work to put stuff
out there that does that and so what
that means is that when people come in
they become a follower they become a
subscriber they're on your email list
you're continuing to send them pieces of
content that service their needs now one
of the best ways to do this is to take a
look at your program or your course and
pull one or two pieces from what you
would charge money for and actually
deliver that for free to people if you
listen to this podcast if you're on this
YouTube channel that's exactly what we
deliver all of our videos that are on
here on this YouTube channel and on my
podcast are some of the highest level
content that you're going to find on
this topic on the internet I'd love to
work with you inside my accelerator
program where we can dive deeper and I
get to work with you and come alongside
you to build your business with you but
I also love the fact that I get to
connect and nurture that relationship
with people through the content that we
deliver and so as a coach and as a
course
creator there's a couple of steps that
we have to take in the process I'm going
to draw it here on the
Whiteboard so step number
one is that we have
to
connect
okay and this is where somebody gets on
your email list after the connection you
want to nurture the relationship and the
nurture process looks like you sending
additional pieces of content that
service what the person needs to solve
in their life and in their business and
you might say Jeremiah I don't have
enough ideas for that I don't it sounds
like too much work can I tell you this
the reason why it's so much work is
often times something that's in our own
head because we want it to be perfect
and we want make sure that it works and
we want to make sure that it delivers on
what we hope and that people will like
it a lot here's the problem with that is
that that is exhausting and that
produces burnout and it's impossible to
nurture a relationship when you see it
as a
task that is hard for you okay now I
don't mean to sound like I have no
empathy for this because I'm actually
somebody who dealt with this issue for a
while and I've actually had ups and
downs where I've dealt with this issue
where I've created content and I put
content out there and I got burnt out
doing the nurture process here's the
reason why I got burnt out because I was
way too concerned with what other people
thought about me I was way too focused
on trying to control the outcome and do
it all perfect and as soon as you let go
of
that which is a skill that you must
learn letting go of perfectionism and
the ability to control what other people
think about you and just put your
content out there those people that
aren't don't want to connect with you
they're not your problem they're not
supposed to be you might say well I just
wish just one person would connect with
me that thinking is why people aren't
connecting with you and so you got to
release that you got to let go of that
and start to become an
attractor to people so when you're an
attractor to people you are attracting
the energy of the person that you're
looking to me make a connection with
people communicate through an exchange
of energy that happens when we speak and
we open our mouths and so the nurture
and the connection happens when we are
speaking and communicating on video to
another person as if we're sitting in
the same room together when you're
watching this video with me it's like
I'm sitting in the same room with you
we're talking together we're sharing
this time we're doing life together now
there might be a couple hundred other
people that watch this video but that's
not what I care about I care about the
connection with one
person and so when you can shrink it
down to what we call the one to many
model one to many you're speaking to one
individual who is exactly the person
that you want to work with the most that
you want to help the most that you want
to understand what you're trying to
accomplish and you're able to connect
with that person where they're at
you're able to deliver exactly what they
desire and then you do that to with
everybody so you speak to one person but
then you send this on your email list to
everybody you post it on your social
media you put it on your
YouTube that nurtures the relationship
and the trust with the people that are
connecting with you and so again one of
the reasons why we fail at this is
because we're trying to control the
outcome too much and we're trying to
make it all perfect now at the same time
you want to set an intention
for the outcome of the nurture you want
to set the intention do the work and
then let go of how it is produced and
analyze the results and see if you need
to make adjustments in the future this
is one of the mistakes that people make
is that they're trying to in the moment
before they create the content make it
all perfect and come up with it in their
mind when in fact what if you just
pressed record what if you just took a
leap of faith and you figured out what's
the topic that I want to talk
about when you can think about who is
the person that you want to help what
are they struggling with and what
strategies do you know that can help
that person accomplish their
goals press record and talk about it
just talk about it like you're sitting
across from
somebody the reason why we can't come up
with ideas is because we're too
concerned about our ideas not being
perfect that's it cuz if you think about
who you want to help who you can help
and you open your mouth to help them as
if they're sitting across you you
imagine in your mind's eye and you might
even open up a photograph of a person or
somebody that could represent that it's
one of the things that I've done is I'll
I'll literally imagine a person that I'm
helping in my mind and I don't concern
myself in the imagining of them doing
the thing that I'm saying I actually
believe and visualize with an intention
in my mind that they're going to do the
thing that I
say that they're going to love what I'm
talking about and I imagine that I'm
talking to somebody who celebrates my
message that loves what I'm talking
about that accepts it that is exactly
qualified for what I'm looking for
whenever I've done that whenever I've
had expectation that people will connect
and they want to listen to what I'm
talking
about it starts to go amazing for me
people love connecting I get all these
different connections tons of people
start to start to want to work with me
but whenever I start to to worry am I
doing it right am I saying the right
thing crickets nothing
happens I've created thousands of videos
and tested this concept and even me
myself I forget
this and I have so much evidence of the
fact that that's really what makes the
biggest difference and so when you can
identify who is the person that I want
to help how can I help them what is a
problem that they're struggling with you
think about who that person is and then
you just start communicating as if
you're in
a a correspondence relationship like
you're sending correspondence messages
you're sending them training you're
sending them Good Vibes you're sending
them the next step of what they should
be doing in their life whenever I make
content I think about what's the next
step that I can help somebody on to
reach their
goals and then we connect with those
people on social media we connect with
them on our email list we connect with
them through Facebook ads to get them to
become clients of ours by attracting
people that are out there into our space
you know we just launched a brand new
Facebook ads class it's completely free
it's over on my website right now if
you're listening to this at the time of
this recording you can go check it
out it'll help you know how to make
connections with new people how to find
those new people what to say what the
exact framework to say is in that
training and if you're in my accelerator
program we work with you through dialing
in your ads and your landing pages and
your offers and knowing exactly how to
bring in the right clients and then how
to create a worldclass coaching system
that people love that gets clients
results and makes you a ton of money in
the
process you don't have to struggle you
don't have to strive to try to make
things work it's possible to get results
when you plug into a proven system like
what we have and like our clients have
like Kim who was able to create over
over 20 ,000 in sales in her real estate
offer or like Ian was able to make
$40,000 a month in his coaching business
following what we're
teaching when you can nurture that
relationship and you you really think
about it like there's a person that's
out there that I want to dive deeper
with them and really start to give them
the best value that I have we're not
holding anything back you know I talked
about this with my group today that
often times we think about well if I
give too much then what do I have to
sell you sell the the the content you
sell your system you sell your process
you pull pieces out of it for the free
content that you're creating but chances
are most people number one when they
watch your free content they're going to
because it's free the human brain will
forget about it I want you to think
about this a lot of the free content
that you've watched you end up
forgetting about and you may maybe pull
one or two nuggets out of but when you
make an investment into something you
really remember it so the idea is is
that if you can actually put great free
content out there but then you ask
people to put some skin in the game to
become a client of yours they will
retain it better when they become a
client and that actually helps them get
the most result even if you're teaching
something that might even be materially
similar to what you gave away for
free and there will be people of course
that be like I'm just going to consume
the free content but they often times
will not get the result that your paid
clients will and that's not your
responsibility to fix that your
responsibility is just to keep showing
up and to keep nurturing that connection
and relationship with the ones that are
meant to work with you so that when
they're ready they will show up when the
student is ready the teacher arrives and
you're already there ready to give them
the results that they're looking for you
know in my accelerator program we work
with people who are ready to actually
get results they're not just dabblers
and so listen I'd love to work with you
in our accelerator program I'd love to
see you in one of our free classes
soon if this podcast has helped you we
got a ton of episodes for coaches and
mentors it's hard being a coach it's
hard being a mentor there's a lot of
stuff that you got to get
right and nowadays it's even more of a
challenge than it ever has been but
that's why I'm here to to help you get
results to help you find the right
clients to finally bring in the revenue
and the cash flow that you want in your
business and make the kind of money that
you want to make so it's my honor thanks
for listening to this stay plugged in
we'll talk soon have a good one
[Music]